<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Work-experiences on UKnowWhoIm</title><link>/work-experience/</link><description>Recent content in Work-experiences on UKnowWhoIm</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/work-experience/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aion Creative Wings</title><link>/work-experience/aion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/work-experience/aion/</guid><description>About This was an intership for a startup of a college senior. We were a team of 10 interns working on different projects.
What did I learn and experience? Flutter from scratch. How to deploy a lightweight app without backend on FireStore. This was my first collaborative project, so I understood all the benefits of a team behind you. What did we build?</description></item><item><title>Pradesh Raksha</title><link>/work-experience/pradesh-rakhsa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/work-experience/pradesh-rakhsa/</guid><description>About This was a voluntary project for Kottayam District Collectorate for managing the COVID situation. I had a great learning experience and a chance to give back to the society.
What did I learn and experience? Went deep into DRF. Experienced a client whose requirements change daily. An oppurtunity to work with a really experienced developer. What did we build? An API for COVID-19 District Management, including Hospital allocation, Ambulance allocation, Storing Patient Data, etc.</description></item><item><title>QAPP</title><link>/work-experience/qapp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/work-experience/qapp/</guid><description>About QAPP was developed during the start of the COVID19 pandemic. We were just 2 developers who built the entire thing, so it taught me very much.
What did I learn and experience? Increased my flutter &amp;amp; DRF proficency. Closely experienced the benefits and problems faced by startups. What did we build? A queue management system for effective social distancing using flutter and DRF.</description></item></channel></rss>